Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world believing.
That surely someday we
just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if waves
are up, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
My head is killing me.
It must have hit it when
we fell or something.
Ah, perhaps the same thing happened to me.
My skull aches terribly.
We've wasted too much time.
I wonder how the samurai's holding up.
I blame you and this stupid side trip. Me?
I thought it was something
we all agreed on.
A shame we weren't able
to locate the yeti.
I thought we were close.
Still, those shadows we saw seemed
quite promising, wouldn't you say?
Those shadows didn't belong to any yeti.
You said yourself that
it was an enemy attack.
No, I did not.
Yes, you did. No, I did not.
I don't believe in the Yeti.
I do believe in Yeti.
I don't believe or disbelieve.
I am content to simply
ponder its existence.
You know, I'm a little
impressed right now.
That's a pretty mature outlook to have.
Well, wisdom is a benefit of advanced age.
Sorry, but I'd call that way of
thinking indecisiveness, not wisdom.
This idiot could fall down the
whole damn mountain for all I care.
Maybe you don't like me, but at
least treat Nami's body with respect.
Will you stop bickering for a
moment and come take a look?
Quickly, I see a footprint.
It's enormous.
Well, what do you think?
This footprint.
Could it have been left
by the legendary Yeti?
Uh-huh.
Not a chance. No way.
Don't be so ridiculous.
Well, damn. It's true.
There are giant footprints in the snow.
Huh?
This is just incredible.
I can't believe it.
There are so many of
them, and they look fresh.
If we follow them, we may find...
One of nature's greatest mysteries.
Looks like they stop here.
Do you see that?
There are two huge shadows behind us!
Oh!
Do you think they could be... Yeti?
What kind of gas is this?
It's almost as if I'm drunk.
I suddenly find it hard to speak
clearly and I'm so very tired.
It's an enemy attack!
Don't waste your time
fighting against the effects.
KYP leaves you drunk and drowsy
no matter how high your tolerance.
Beneath this cliff lies District F-16.
Home to the terrible ice spikes.
Three targets down.
Huh?
Spikes!
Hey guys, any ideas?
Well, that was a close call.
We have arrived at District F-16.
We found three of the
Straw Hats as reported.
We will recover the dead bodies.
Huh?
Hate to disappoint you.
Hey, one of them's alive!
She's just a girl.
She won't bite us.
I wouldn't be so sure if I were you.
Damn underlings!
I have to be more careful.
Nami's body is fragile.
It probably bruises easily.
I don't want to put a
single scratch on it.
I need a smoke, Nami, my love.
Sorry.
And now?
Time to wake up, you idiot!
Anyway, enough hunting nature's mysteries.
Think the samurai's around here somewhere?
Yeah, that would make
the most sense, at least.
I'd imagine he's probably still looking
for his torso in the vicinity of the lake.
We're not far from the water now.
Can you hear us, samurai?
Hey! Samurai!
Come out, come out, wherever you are!
Samurai!
Did someone kick your ass already?
You've got to be here somewhere.
Answer us!
Hello?
If you're able, please say something.
I truly thought we would find him here.
Who knows, maybe you found his torso
already and went off to look for his son?
Hey, guys, I think this is him! What?
Well, crap, he's frozen solid.
One, two, three!
Hey, you all right?
You don't look too good.
So someone did kick your ass.
I suddenly became paralyzed.
I thought for certain
that death was upon me.
You mean you got caught in
a snowstorm and froze solid?
No!
The cold cannot touch me!
Quit being so stubborn!
A warrior such as I
does not feel the cold!
This guy's more trouble than he's worth.
Whip up some clothes, or have you
already forgotten your ability?
The truth is, the magic, I did
not acquire it without a cost.
Because of it, I now
have a certain weakness.
I will ever since partaking of that
fruit, when submerged in water, I...
You can't swim, right?
Yeah, we know.
Well, you see, I believe I
may know where my torso is.
I...
I suspect that you might
locate it somewhere underwater.
Underwater?
Yes, that's right.
It feels as if the upper
half of my body is submerged.
I see.
So that's how you wound up
here, immobilized and frozen.
If your body is underwater,
then you can't use your ability.
You said his torso was near the lake.
If it's stumbling around
headless, it may have fallen in.
That's possible.
And I believe the lake is
salt water rather than fresh.
Well, his other bits are
still alive and kicking,
so I think we can assume it
hasn't become shark food yet.
But we have no idea what kind
of creatures are in that lake.
We better get it out as soon as possible.
That's true.
We should waste no time. I...
I fear that I must ask if you
would be willing to, uh...
Just ask already, damn
stubborn samurai. We'll do it.
But aren't you people pirates?
And I am another stranger to you.
So why are you so willing to aid me?
When I saved your head, I
became responsible for you.
But know this.
When you're back in one
piece, we will fight.
And I will kick your ass.
I...
I accept your aid and your challenge.
You have my gratitude.
Well, well.
Look at who learned how to say thank you.
the cold taught you manners what
do you know what's that oh it's
difficult to tell oh those look
like centaurs perhaps the ones
we robbed Brownbeard subordinates
stay with me keep running we
have to get away from the lake
now and away from the monster that
appeared on the other side how
has it been hiding on the island
all this time if we could just
make it to the master he'll know
what to do save your breath and
focus on running if we slow down
at all it'll get us what scared of
a monster aren't you monsters too
them again those are the pirates
who robbed us damn you're right
that one's wearing my coat forget
about them just run let's get
to the lab don't forget they
kidnapped boss
what's
got them so
worked up they seem to be running
from something hmm they look scared
all right and they were coming
from the lake the one we saw
earlier right brooke what yes that's
correct the lake's that way the
same direction we were headed why
what are you thinking Zoro well
if it is actually the same lake
where did that mountain come from
oh how strange wait that's
not a mountain what the hell
Shrororororororororororororororororororororoo
Riley was the so-called
chemical weapon explosion
that occurred four years ago
right here on Punkhazard.
Did they seriously believe I would purify
the island of my experiment entirely?
Who would be so wasteful?
Well, instead I created a monster
by compressing all the gas.
And it lives here still my
smiley yes punk acid became
uninhabitable a Wasteland covered
with a blanket of death the
poisonous threat seemed to
Disappear with my arrival in truth
it's been lingering here all
along waiting to Be unleashed?
We did it!
We got their ship!
Don't let them get out to sea!
Finish them off!
Let's end this quickly! Smoker!
I don't know what I'm doing!
How do I turn back?
You're getting in the way!
Just stay still for right now!
Come on, you idiots!
Get that door open!
That rat is hiding out in his lab.
We can't exterminate him
all the way out here.
It's no use, Smokey.
The door won't budge. Sorry.
Damn it all.
If only I were in my own body,
I could get inside there easily.
Instead, I'm stuck like this.
That was awesome your power is
super cool did we just teleport?
Shut up and stay inside the bag.
We've almost reached the back door of the
lab they should be
working in the main room.
Caesar and probably that
bird woman here's what
we do try to find a way to
get them out of this. place.
While we're gone, you look around and
see what you can learn about the drug.
I don't understand.
It seems like you've got pretty
easy access to the Master.
And your
power is strong.
Wouldn't it be simpler to
go ahead and capture him?
Then we'd have plenty
of time to find out about the drug.
I can't take him down myself.
There are certain circumstances
preventing that, which
is why I involved you.
You don't need to know the specifics.
All All I'm asking your
crew to do is kidnap him.
I'll take care of the rest.
Hey, you guys!
Look over there!
What in the hell is that thing?
It's headed right for us!
Is it some kind of missile?
No, it's not a missile!
Now, the end flow, weep!
What the hell?
It talked!
But missiles can't talk.
Damn.
Killer shortcut there, Luffy!
Or else we'll break into your lab
before we kick your ass and kidnap you?
Luffy, that was supposed
to be secret, him again.
Crap!
It's the straw hair crew.
Go, Luffy, go!
Damn loudmouth.
Are you capable of doing anything quietly?
Where are you, master?
Show yourself!
Hey guys, did that bastard just say he's
gonna kick our master's ass and kidnap him?
Yeah, like hell.
Down with the saw hats, let's go!
Ghostrun...
right!
We're here.
How long do you think we'll
have to wait for the master?
I doubt he intends to
walk out and greet us.
Okay.
What now?
Do we look for him in the laboratory?
Sounds good.
That door over there is
probably the entrance.
Right.
Shall we go? Well.
Straw Hat Luffy.
Tell me this.
What is your crew doing here?
Why so mad?
He looked better than I thought
you would last time I saw you.
You were I'm getting beat up pretty bad.
Stop messing with me.
What's wrong?
Constipated or something?
You feel like gassy?
Take that!
You didn't used to be this weak.
Did something happen to you?
Get off of me! Let go!
Not just weak, you sound different too,
almost like you're a girl or something.
Hey Toshiki, do me a favor.
Don't get your ass kicked by an idiot
like him while you're in my body, okay?
Hey, that weapon!
Straw Hat Luffy, back at sea.
Causing trouble. Too bad.
I'm here now to put an end to your fun.
Crap! I got hit!
The things tip with Z-prisms don't...
I remember her!
It's that lady captain with the glasses!
She gets so strong!
Huh!
The name's Smoker, Straw Hat!
Don't you see?
They're both victims of lost little trick.
Oh, the whole shovel thing?
Okay, that explains why he was so weak.
So this girl is...
Oh, wow.
Nice luck, Smokey!
What's so funny, you little maggot?
No more dodging! Come fight me!
Second gear!
He's moving too fast.
We'll finish this another time, Kay. What?
I'd rather fight you when you
can use all your strength.
It's more fun that way.
I don't need charity.
We fight now!
Goodbye, Smokey!
See ya!
And go Radical Bee!
He blasted a hole in it!
How strong are they?
Oh, is that a laser?
Luffy! Robin!
The lab door's open now!
Let's go in and say hi!
Woohoo!
Way to use that laser! Yeah!
Smokey!
There's something strange
flying at us, sir!
It's up there!
What the...
What is that? The ship!
Luffy, Franky, wait a minute.
What's happening?
It's getting harder to breathe.
Poison gas, Jordan, heal it.
It started leaking after we cut it
open and filled it with bullet holes.
We need our gas masks.
Quick, let's go.
Whoa!
That looks crazy!
Is it alive?
Perhaps it's some kind of monster.
It moves on its own.
Tell me, where did that
thing come from? I...
I have no idea.
I've never seen it before.
It just came falling out of the sky.
Yeah, and now it's all over the ship!
Whatever it is, it's disgusting!
It's got eyes that means
it's some creature right.
Hey look the blobs are
merging it's getting bigger.
I bet it can't swim let's
try pushing it into water.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
It's leaking gas again!
Get him out!
One, two, three!
Crap.
So what now?
Ow!
It's on my skin!
Somebody get it off! Hurry!
We need some cloth!
You see?
I knew we shouldn't
have touched that thing!
So what do we do?
How should I know?
I've got this boys.
Stay back we haven't seen if
it likes fire yet have we?
I say we give it a try.
There's nothing in the world
that's not afraid of fire.
Good idea smart gun the sucker.
I'm gonna kill this slime monster.
Won't be long now.
Things gotta be hurting right?
Starting to burn.
No, damn you!
So, anyone know what that thing is?
Some kind of slimy blob monster.
Touch it and spears boys
and burn it and it explodes.
Is it dead?
Or was it alive in the first place?
Doesn't matter.
It's gone now, right? Yeah. Right.
That's good, huh?
More than good.
That explosion saved
us the trouble of going
after the navy bastards
who stole our ship.
It did us a favor.
It's back!
There's more!
Going this way!
Falling out of the sky like before!
How many are there?
Look out! There's one coming!
Run away!
Don't let him touch you!
Smoker, quick!
It's too dangerous to stay!
Retreat and find cover!
Good boy, I'm sorry I had to keep
you locked up for three years.
Master, you should go sir,
it isn't safe here now?
Just like I thought.
It is Caesar Clown.
He's the one behind this.
Are you the master?
That's it!
You're going down!
Master of Punk Hazard!
Straw Hat Pirates and Marines of
the Navy G5, welcome to my island!
Allow me to present the most
brilliant scientist ever!
I am Caesar Clown!
A bit of patience, it won't be long.
He doesn't tolerate
water very well, you see.
So in order to cross the lake, he has
to fling himself over piece by piece.
Inconvenient, perhaps,
but effective nonetheless.
From a land of blazing fire
to a land of sparkling ice.
In a few minutes, he will be fully
reassembled on this side of the lake.
And then, boys and girls,
the show will begin!
A recreation of the explosion from four
years ago, and you have front row seats!
Now, prepare for destruction on a scale
that you've never witnessed before!
So is it uh living i have
no clue i've never seen
anything like it this is
such a shocking sight?
My eyes might pop out of my head
no they won't but i haven't got any
Well whatever it is it's strange
whatever it's doing is even stranger!
I got you now, Master!